

# Vipul Shukla

A passionate Full Stack Web Developer

Download CV

#### **About Me**

Hello! I'm Vipul Shukla. I am a passionate Full Stack Web Developer having an experience of building Web applications with JavaScript / Reactjs / Nodejs / Laravel / Python / Flask and some other cool libraries and frameworks.

Age 23

Email vipul71098@gmail.com

Phone +91-6306751110

Address 5B/E -19 vrindavan yojna, lucknow

# **Professional Skills**



# Other Cool stuffs













# **Work Experience**

#### Full STack Developer at Opiniofi Technologies Pvt Ltd, survaider Bangalore

May.2018 - july.2018

As a part of internship program, I was selected for the position of Full Stack Developer I worked on both on front end and backend of the survaider app assisting senior developers, which are build on Angularjs and Flask respectively. It was a paid internship and they paid 15000 Rs.

#### Major Tasks on internship

- 1. Creating a JS app to find online review links for business and creating a downloadable file.
- 2. Creating a python backend app to Scrape online ratings and compute score for a business.
- 3. Assisting development teams with day to day task.

#### Full Stack Developer at ENTERUX SOLUTION

May 15 2020 - august 2020

As a part of internship program, I was selected for the position of Full Stack Developer I worked on both on front end and backend of the enterux app & website, which are build on react-native and nodejs respectively. It is a paid internship and they paying 15000 Rs per month..

#### Major Tasks on internship

- 1. Create a library for calculating data consumption on webrtc video call.
- 2. mplement socket on their Kyc Product.
- 3. Designing layouts of product in react native
- Designing & managing their website.
- 5. Creating front end of their App in react native.

#### Full Stack Developer at Stimulus Consultancy, Ahmedabad

Jan, 2021 - persent

#### Major task on Job

#### **HubSpot Integration**

- . Integrating APIs with web applications
- · Automation of HubSpot Workflow
- . Integrating APIs with web applications
- Fetching and displaying HubSpot data on client side
- Customization

#### **VoIP Telephony Management Tool**

- · Getting devices from Net Sapiens
- · Getting and managing voice mails
- . Managing Sip Trunks
- User Access Management
- Generating Reports

#### Online Survey

- Creating online survey
- Creation Questionnaire from Customer Portal
- · Answer reviews from Admin Portal
- Modular APi Creation for different modules
- Database Management

#### Nettoken

- Desgining UI
- managing Chrome extension
- · Add Accounts related functionality
- · Managing web, extension and mobile app sync

#### Netvisor

- Integration of Netvisor
- Creat Api in Netvisor
- Managing Netvisor

# Education

### Bachelor of Computer Science from MIMIT College (Punjab)

2016 - 2020

Completed Bachelor from MIMIT clg(punjab) with overall 6.4 CGPA.

## Senior Secondary School Examination from CBSE.Board (Maths)

2014 - 2016

Completed my 12th from Kendriya Vidhalay SGPGI(Lucknow) with 74%.

### Higher Secondary School Examination from CBSE.Board

2012 - 2014

Compeletd my 10th from St Francis mission school (lucknow) with 90%.

# Vipul Shukla





